所以作为一个应用程序的采访者，你在找什么 ?
So as the interviewer on an application,
what are you looking for?
在你事业中的某个阶段如果你搬到你去的地方
Cuz some point in your careers, if you
move up to the place where you're doing
雇佣的人很可能也会有很多人最终会在那里
hiring and probably a lot of you are,
will be there eventually.
当你看一个简历时，想想这个人的角色是什么样的，
When you look at a resume,
think what sort of roles this person fit,
他们有什么样的经历
what sort of experiences they have?
那么，这一个是关键的，他们需要什么样的经验 ?
And then, this one is critical,
what sort of experience do they need?
老实说如果有人建了静态网页
And be honest,
if someone's building static webpages,
他们需要一个 CS 学位和十年的经验吗 ?
do they need a CS degree and
ten years experience?
可能不，老实说，我见过很多工作
Probably not, lets be honest about this,
I've seen many jobs for
需要 CS 学位和 4 年经验的初级实习生。
junior intern engineer needing a CS
degree and like four years experience.
来吧，来吧，来吧，真正的问题是，
Like come on, come on,
[LAUGH] and the real question is,
你的选择有什么偏差吗
is there any bias in your selection?
你只看那些去常春藤联赛的人吗
Are you only looking at people
that went to Ivy Leagues?
你只找男人吗
Are you only looking for men?
你是在找和你住同一地方的人吗
Are you only looking for
people that live in the same place as you?
你是在找来自你的国家的人吗
Are you only looking for people who
are from the country that you're from?
您的选择过程是否存在偏差 ?
Is there bias in your selection process?
我保证有些人都是人类
I guarantee there's some,
we're all human but
最好的事情就是承认
the best thing to do is acknowledge it.
然后说我能做些什么来缓解这个问题呢 ?
And then say what can
I do to mitigate this?
而这对每一家公司来说都是真实的
And this is true of every company, many,
很多招聘经理就像我只想要这些标准。
many hiring managers are like
I only want these criteria.
杰姆我找不到合格的工程师
Jem, I can't find qualified engineers.
你在找什么
What are you looking for?
我在找几个去哈佛的人
Well, I'm looking for few that went to
Harvard, and had a 4.0 GPA, and maybe like
他们的名字就像他们的名字一样祝你好运
a patent or two for their name like,
well, good luck with that, and I move on.
坦白地说你想雇用什么样的工程师
Be honest with yourself about what
sort of engineers you wanna hire and
你的工程师想和你一起工作
what's your engineers you wanna work with.
是否符合您要查找的条件 ?
Would you fit the criteria
that you're looking for?
这些都是要考虑的原因，因为在你的职业生涯的某个时候，
These are things to think about
because at some point in your career,
你可能要雇个人来找简历
you will probably have to hire somebody
and you're looking at resumes.
所以现在开始思考你在寻找什么东西。
So start thinking now about what
sort of things you're looking for.